<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on QUAY Financials</title>
    <link>https://quay.cicy.de/tags/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on QUAY Financials</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 11:18:56 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://quay.cicy.de/tags/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Exchange</title>
      <link>https://quay.cicy.de/blog/foreign-exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 11:18:56 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quay.cicy.de/blog/foreign-exchange/</guid>
      <description>Foreign Exchange FX Trading:
Quay Financials is able to offer hedge funds, asset managers and professional traders access to a 24-hour inter-bank FX trading environment online or via phone in spot, forward and option contracts. Quay Financials’ FX trading desks are run by market professionals with over 20 years of experience covering all of our clients’ needs from execution to currency delivery (if required). Quay Financials’ global market coverage is key to our service, backed up with the ability to update on relevant market news throughout the day and night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Futures and Options</title>
      <link>https://quay.cicy.de/blog/futures-and-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 11:18:32 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quay.cicy.de/blog/futures-and-options/</guid>
      <description>Futures &amp;amp; Options Quay Financials provides you with a personalised global stock broking service that uses the clearing and custodian facilities of industry leaders.
We offer execution only and advisory brokering services.
The more experienced client, whether investor or trader, requires a comprehensive and efficient service that ensures trades are executed and settled in the most efficient manner possible.
Other individuals and professional intermediaries require a basic service where they can give simple instructions to purchase or sell securities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Securities</title>
      <link>https://quay.cicy.de/blog/securities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 11:16:38 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://quay.cicy.de/blog/securities/</guid>
      <description>Securities Quay Financials provides you with a personalised global stock broking service that uses the clearing and custodian facilities of industry leaders.
We offer execution only and advisory brokering services.
The more experienced client, whether investor or trader, requires a comprehensive and efficient service that ensures trades are executed and settled in the most efficient manner possible.
Other individuals and professional intermediaries require a basic service where they can give simple instructions to purchase or sell securities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
